What's this?
What shall I do?
Even the obvious things are always so hard
I just want to grin when I'm happy, sing when I'm in love
They say my dreams will come true someday
but when will someday come? I can't wait!
Count one, two, three and spread my arms
Gather the light to myself
Where is it? Tell me what I can do
Even if I'm hurt so much, even if I run so hard
Even if I collapse crying over and over, I still
believe in my amazing future
... Spring's Pitter-patter.
Hey, Kobato, who did you give chocolate to?
Me?
I gave some to, uhh...
Miss Sayaka, and Ioryogi, and Toshihiko...
I didn't mean it like that! The one you were saving for the person you really like, who'd you give that to?
I really like everyone here, so...
C'mon!
Well...
Sorry to butt in while you're having fun.
You don't need to be that worried.
Go get Sayaka for me.
What are you here for?
I came to have a chat.
For the last time.
No!
That's nice. Now be a dear and move.
I will not!
That's too bad.
Kobato.
It's okay. Let him by.
It's been a while, Sayaka.
Please. Just give us a little longer.
How long is a little?
I think I've waited long enough.
Why have you changed so much?
I haven't changed. This is the real me.
Liar...
Just give up.
Are you just being stubborn because of me?
You've got it all wrong.
You're not my problem anymore.
Which means I'm just here to finish things.
Or would you rather I have the place demolished with the children watching?
I don't get why you're so fixated on this place. You can always open a nursery somewhere else.
Fujimoto!
What are you talking about!?
You should know!
Fujimoto!
This isn't just a building!
It's Sayaka's inheritance! It's important to her!
She can't just go somewhere else!
If you're going to go on like that, what are you really worried about protecting?
Do you care more about the building than the children?
If you don't care what happens to the kids, you may as well stay.
But that would really be a case of mistaken priorities.
You-
Don't!
If you stick your nose in where it doesn't belong, things will just speed up.
Understood.
I'll shut down.
Miss Sayaka...
But give me until graduation.
What's Dobato up to, anyway?
Hey.
Come on, you.
We just dried the sheets, and now you're getting them wet again.
I'm sorry...
Hmph.
You're just making more work for me.
I'm so sorry!
I'm going to go see Okiura.
What will you do when you get there?
I'll ask him one more time not to shut down Yomogi Nursery.
You're just going to make more of a mess out of things.
But if we just-
Don't go, okay?
Hey.
You're-
What's he up to all of a sudden?
What good would knowing do you?
This is extortion.
If we wanted to, we'd have you in court.
Yeah, I'd like to see that happen.
Plus, Teach there is going along with it.
You should just shut up and move on.
I won't give up. I'm going to protect that nursery.
Oh yeah? How?
You don't know anything about what's going on, you idiot.
Wait! I'm not done talking to you!
What are you doing, trying to look cool saving everyone?
You're wasting your time whining at me.
Listen. The one who's really after that nursery is the boss.
The boss?
Okiura's old man.
He's the one who got the old headmaster in debt, too.
You mean-
It's his fault the headmaster was stuck running around raising money like that...
He worked himself to death believing in that!
If he knew that and went along with his father anyway, he's just as bad!
Didn't I tell you you didn't know anything!?
Do you know what would happen if the boss got involved?
That's why Okiura is dealing with it himself.
I...
I think Okiura is playing the villain to protect that nursery from the boss.
If I had to guess, probably to protect the woman he loves.
Don't give me that crap!
Believe whatever you want.
But I owe that Kobato girl.
I don't want her to get hurt if this turns sour.
So you'd better do what Okiura says.
...of the mountain, we can see everything
Let's look, look for new mysteries!
All the other nurseries are full.
I'm on the waiting lists, too.
I'm sorry this happened.
All right, dinner's served!
This is-
How about having dinner with us?
It's less lonely if we all eat together!
Chise...
I'm sorry, but...
I can't eat food.
I know how you feel. I don't think any of us are really in the mood for a meal right now.
No, I mean...
I'm really happy you want to share!
Daddy... I'm sorry.
I wasn't able to protect the nursery.
Even after all this, I still want to believe in him.
I'm so silly, aren't I?
Chitose...
I saw Okiura in front of the nursery today.
He seemed so lonely.
Oh...
He's the one who wanted us gone, too.
Maybe he still loves Sayaka.
Maybe she still loves him.
Then why would he make her so sad?
Sometimes, because people love each other... Because they care about each other...
That means they misunderstand each other.
That's him!
If I follow him, I can meet Okiura!
Hey...
Excuse me!
Let me talk with Mr. Okiura!
You should stay away from me, girl.
Please!
He's not going to see you. Go home.
Wait!
That girl from the nursery followed me her. It probably won't be easy to get her to go away.
Then just ignore her.
She's still there.
Okiura?
Is everyone from the nursery that much of a pain in the ass?
Aren't you cold, Ioryogi?
Of course I am!
If you can tell, whe don't you go borrow an umbrella or wait inside for a while?
C'mon, use your head!
But what if Okiura looks out the window and sees that I'm not here?
If you keep this up, he's never coming out.
He'll come out eventually. If not today, tomorrow.
If not tomorrow, the day after.
How long are you going to wait?
As long as it takes for him to show his face.
Are you going to keep doing that forever?
Okiura! I-
I don't have anything to say to you.
We're tearing down that nursery, and the lot's worth enough to cover the loan.
That should settle everything.
That's not what I wanted to ask you about.
I want to know how you really feel!
I told you, the nursery-
That's not what I mean!
You're such a pain.
Chitose told me.
About you and Sayaka, and about Sayaka and you.
That you both still love each other.
I didn't expect you to talk about that.
Okiura!
If Sayaka's that important to you, why are you so mean to her!
We all loved it...
Sayaka, me, Fujimoto...
Everyone at Yomogi...
We all loved it!
So...
That's why Sayaka tried to hard to protect it.
But you still took it away from her.
You made Miss Sayaka sad.
I can't believe you're a good person anymore.
But even if you're not a good person, you're important to Miss Sayaka.
You can't just leave things like this!
Please, tell me!
We just came from different worlds.
I couldn't hold back my father any more.
So this is the only way I can protect her.
You couldn't just abandon Miss Sayaka, could you?
You ended things because she was so important to you...
Hey!
Sayaka.
Fujimoto...
I'm sorry, I couldn't sleep.
You too, huh?
Sayaka...
He dragged himself through the mud to protect you.
Fujimoto, what are you-
Okiura.
He-
But... I still can't forgive-
What are you saying!?
If you don't forgive him, he's just going to go away!
Are you okay with that!?
Come on.
I want you to be happy.
He's the only one that can help you.
So you have to be with him.
But...
I'm glad you're awake.
Miss Sayaka...
He said you sere out in the rain for a while.
Everyone always ends up protecting me.
Kobato, Fujimoto...
And him...
Where's Okiura!?
He went home.
Are you just going to leave it like that!?
Miss Sayaka...
If you really care about Okiura, you need to go after him!
Hurry!
It's gonna be close.
Don't forget about your wish.
In between the things I've lost
and the things I've been able to hold on to,
Your smile falls in that gap
It seems like I can reach it, but I can't
I can't fly
I just wanted to make you smile
My two wings weren't good enough
Why do I even have them?
Just smiling by your side
is all I can do.
Just warming you is good enough,
even though I want to embrace you
Even with these scarred, worthless wings,
right now I can smile
Next episode: "Day of Farewells"